Rob Letts

Front-End Web Developer

Email: roblettsdev@gmail.com

Phone: +447449983319 Location: London, UK GitHub: rob-letts

LinkedIn: robertletts Site: robletts.dev



HTML



CSS



SCSS



JavaScript



TypeScript



Vite



Vue.js



Cypress



Figma

Bio

Front-End Web Developer based in South London, specialising in modern CSS, design systems and component libraries, and the Vue.js ecosystem.

Advocate for universal accessibility and utilising platform standards to sustainably further positive web experiences.

Conscious and empathetic individual that prioritises open communication and empowering colleagues. Previous career in live events and music venue management.

Employment

TixTrack - Front End Engineer

June 2022 - Present

UI/UX and Design System specialist within a Front End Team migrating and extending an existing Angular monolith to a new Vue architecture, for international ticketing solutions for live events and museums primarily for Broadway NYC and London's West End theatres.

Red Snapper - Junior Front-End Web Developer October 2021 - June 2022

Using Vue.js, SCSS, and TailwindCSS to implement dynamic UIs for Laravel and in-house CMS back-ends, as well as standalone microsites, for the London-based web design and development agency offering web implementations and consultancy for a variety of clients, including the BBC and British Medical Journal.

Corsica Studios - Assistant General Manager

March 2012 - November 2020

Overseeing a team of 50 to ensure safe running of live music events for crowds of 1000+. Co-ordinating and engineering audio-visual equipment and technical requirements for international musicians and artists, as well as training and developing staff, for an independent arts and music organisation.

Education

MSc, Computer Science - Distinction September 2020 - September 2021 Birkbeck, University of London

BA (Hons), Music and Sonic Media - Merit September 2010 - June 2013 London South Bank University